翻譯: Bay
早上好 Mike.
Morning, Mike.
嘿 星球大戰新的生物出現了
Hey, the new star wars creatures are out.
校對: LOS LOS LOS
Rags最近不太舒服
Rags hasn't been feeling well lately,
后期: 東仔線代掛科不高興
我不能把他單獨留在家里 所以我就...
and I can't exactly leave him home alone, so I thought...
別說了 別說了
say no more, say no more.
壓制: 猴給力
我就知道這一天會到來的
I knew this day would come.
禁止攜帶有自殺傾向的狗
這牌子上寫的很清楚
What does that sign say?
Mike  它沒有自殺傾向
Mike, he's not suicidal.
Carter 上一次他來辦公室
Carter, last time he was here,
就試圖上碎紙機
he tried to hump the paper shredder.
就這樣吧
So, that's it.
好吧 Mike 在這件事上你可大錯特錯了
Well... You're way off base on this, Mike.
現在的Rags就像23年前一樣快樂
Rags is as happy today as he was 23 years ago.
真的
Really?
一定很疼吧
Now that had to hurt.
政界小人物
第三季 第十八集
電波誠譯
這太棒了 Marie阿姨
This was so great, aunt Marie.
感謝您的來訪
Thank you so much for visiting.
我玩的很開心 Stace 真的
I had a great time, stace, I really did.
你看 那個你讓我做的必做事項表
And look, that things-to-do list you made me?
我每項都完成了
I checked off every one.
你知道嗎 Marie
You know, Marie?
你在這的整個期間
The whole time you were here,
都完全對我視而不見
you completely ignored me.
完成一項
Check.
聽著 我得趕飛機了
Listen, I gotta catch a plane.
見到大家很高興
Nice meeting you all.
這是怎么回事
What was that?
什么
What?
你倆的表情 我了解這種表情
That look between you. I know that look.
是下流的表情
That's a dirty look.
Stuart 我都不知道下流表情是什么樣的
Stuart, I don't even know what a dirty look is.
我做給你看
Let me show you.
哦 太下流了
Ooh, that's so seedy.
我還沒做呢
I haven't even done it yet.
嘿 Owen在嗎
Hey, is... is Owen here yet?
第一百萬次告訴你了 不在
For the millionth time, no.
他一到我就會通知你的
I will buzz you the second he gets here.
天哪 我從來沒見過你這么興奮
Jeez, I've never seen you so excited.
你看起來像個小女孩
You're like a little girl
在等他因為毆打警察被判刑的哥哥出獄
the morning her brother gets out of jail for beating up a cop.
或者是圣誕節早晨
Or Christmas morning.
我只是有些緊張
I'm a little nervous, that's all.
Owen可是我的導師
This guy, you know, Owen, was my mentor.
他教會了我關于政治的一切
He taught me everything I know about politics.
如何競選
How to campaign...
如何操縱媒體
How to manipulate the press...
最重要的 如何鼓動大眾
Most importantly, how to motivate people,
當他到達時 我希望大家
so when he gets here, I want you guys to all...
你知道的 呃 做事
You know... Uh, do... do stuff.
Michael Flaherty
Michael Flaherty!
演員Christopher Lloyd  在<回到未來>系列中扮演布朗博士
Owen Kingston
Owen Kingston!
哦 看看你 我就知道
Ohhhh, look at you. I tell ya.
這就像 呃 回到過去
This is, uh... this is like stepping back in time.
對話出自兩人合作的<回到未來>系列
過去只是序章 Michael
The past is prologue, Michael.
像我們這樣的人得面向
Men like us have to keep looking...
未來
To the future.
你到底說什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?
我不知道
I don't know.
我第一次招Michael時他還是個實習生
When I first hired Michael as an intern
他那時經常早早溜進辦公室
he used to sneak into the office early
然后假裝自己是參議員
and play senator.
我想開除他 但他那時已經
I tried to fire him, but by that time
參與制定通過一些重要的法案
he had already passed some significant legislation.
我不覺得有多重要
I wouldn't call it significant.
紅燈亮起時允許右轉 是我干的
Uh, right on red? That was me.
甜甜圈來了
Donuts are here!
嗨 好耶 好耶
Hey! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
等下 等下
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
首先 要表達謝意
First, let us give thanks.
對 Stacy 多謝
Yeah, ok. Hey, Stacy, thanks a lot.
我要吃鈴鐺圈
I get the twisty one.
我的意思是通過禱告
I meant, uh, with prayer.
Michael
Michael?
呃 Stacy 你來吧
Uh, Stacy, wh-why don't you do it?
絕不
Hell, no.
我來
I'll go.
哦 主啊 祝福這饋贈
Oh, lord, bless this bounty,
讓我們贊美您的榮耀
and let us revel in your glory
我們
for...
只是可憐的罪人
For we are but wretched sinners...
不值得擁有您神圣的仁愛
Who are not worthy of your divine benevolence.
放松 只是些甜甜圈
Relax, kid. They're just donuts.
Paul 謝謝你同意把Rags藏在這里
Paul, thanks for hiding Rags in here.
我真的很感謝
I really appreciate it.
Carter 我們可是朋友
Carter, please, we're friends.
用錢謝就夠了
Your money is thanks enough.
這些藥是治它的
Ok, these are his pills for
瘙癢 哮喘 腹瀉
itching, wheezing, and diarrhea.
這是抗真菌的
This is his anti-fungal cream.
每天兩次抹在它肚子上
Rub that on his tummy twice a day.
轉圈抹
He likes a circular motion,
別上下抹 它會吐的
not up and down or he'll vomit.
這要可以減少它的胃脹氣
This ointment reduces flatulence.
用手指蘸一點 輕輕地
You dip your finger in here... lightly,
像這樣 然后溫柔的抹在它的肛門周圍
like so... and rub it gently on his rectum.
這得加錢
I'm gonna need more money.
我會坐另一輛車
So I'll take a separate car
然后和你在大廈見面 共進晚餐如何
and meet you at the mansion for dinner?
很好
Excellent.
Janelle 自從我們約會以來
And, Janelle, since we've started dating,
我知道我們的生活開始充滿了秘密的計劃
I know our lives have become full of secret plans
鬼鬼祟祟的見面 神秘的化名
and furtive meetings, mysterious code names.
是啊 我知道 有些囧
Yeah, I know. It can be a little awkward.
哦 其實我想說的是這挺酷的
Well, I was gonna say it's pretty cool.
我感覺像個間諜
I feel like a spy.
我們今晚再見 Randall
Well, I'll see you tonight, Randall.
你可以叫我性感特工
Well, you can call me double-o sexy.
先生 還記得 Owen Kingston嗎
Sir, you remember Owen Kingston.
當然  我知道
Of course. Well, I understand
你是為了千年發展計劃而來的
you're heading up our millennium project.
市長先生 這是我的榮幸
Mr. Mayor, it is a great honor.
很高興又見到Mike吧
Good to see Mike again, huh?
是啊 哈哈
Yeah, ha ha.
我覺得我培養的這個人還不錯
I feel like I did a good job on this one.
是嗎 是你培養的嗎
Really? You did?
有意思
Interesting.
Mike有次曾私下和我說過一句話
You know, something Mike told me personally
當時可是我一生的驕傲之一 他說
was one of my proudest moments, and I quote,
"我本會學習如何在政界"
"I could have learned to crawl "
"摸爬滾打"
"through the world of politics "
"但是你卻教會我"
"but you were the one"
如何像個男人堂堂正正行走于政界"
who taught me how to walk like a man."
誰能想到當年這句話現在會
Who would have thought that was gonna come back
反過來讓我難堪
and bite me on the ass?
先生 議員Donne希望與您見面
Sir, councilman Donne would like to have a word with you.
我會處理的 先生
Uh, I'll handle that, sir.
我聽說你離開政界有些日子了
So, I hear you've been out of the game for awhile.
確定你還能像Mike說的那么敏銳嗎
Are you sure you're still as sharp as Mike says?
你和你秘書約會多久了
How long you been dating your secretary?
大約一周
About a week.
James 這地方真的很討人喜歡
James, I think this place is really adorable.
你笑什么呢
What's so funny?
我床上有個女人
There's a woman on my bed.
James 我不希望令你緊張什么的
Look, James, I don't want to make you nervous or anything,
即使我約會過不少男人
but even though I've dated a lot of men,
我從沒和他們睡過 我也不知道為什么
I've never slept with one. I mean, I don't know,
也許我這一生都在等待那個對的人
maybe it's because I've waited my whole life for the right guy.
所以 我是那個對的人?
So, I'm the right guy?
不 我就是等厭煩了
No, I'm just really sick of waiting.
教我一切 James
Teach me everything, James.
我的意思是 我甚至不知道做愛需要多長時間
I mean, I don't even know how long sex is supposed to take.
一般男人 可以堅持6到7分鐘
Well, with your average guy, it can last, like, 6 or 7 minutes.
我么 我只需要一半的時間
Me... I can have you out of here in half that time.
哦 電話
Ah, phone.
答錄機會接的吧
Won't the machine answer that?
答錄機 你以為我是George Jetson嗎
Machine? Who am I, George Jetson?
George Jetson 科幻動畫片<杰森一家>人物
什么答錄機 Marie
Machine. Marie.
記住 James 我剛離開
Remember, James. I've just left town.
沒人知道我在這
No one knows I'm here.
別擔心 沒事
Don't worry. I'll be cool.
喂
Hello?
James 我是Stuart
James, it's Stuart.
嘿 讓 Stacy的阿姨接電話
Hey, let me speak to Stacy's aunt.
好的 找你的
Sure. It's for you.
我就知道
I knew it!
你的朋友Owen似乎
So, your friend Owen seems...
我不知道
I don't know...
有點不正常
A little out there.
Carter 這只是第一印象
Carter, that's just a first impression.
你第一次見我時 你覺得我是
When you first met me, you thought I was, what?
一個控制狂 希望身邊所有人都言聽計從
A control freak who wanted to surround himself with yes men.
- 對不對  - 是的  Mike
- Am I right?  - Yes, Mike.
你不認為Owen有點
Don't you think Owen seemed a little, uh, I don't know...
過于篤信宗教
Overly religious?
他信教 這又如何
He found religion, so what?
我還希望有朝一日我能找到信仰呢
Hope to find religion myself someday.
你知道 當我老了時
You know, when I'm older
快死時
and looking to cut a deal.
嘿 Mike
Hey, Mike.
那是一個普通人在接杯水
That's a normal guy getting a glass of water.
- 嘿 Carter  - Owen
- Hey, Carter.  - Owen.
哦 黑暗的家伙
Ooh. A dark one.
惡魔
Evil.
好
Yes.
你喜歡這樣 是不是
You like this, don't you?
是的 你喜歡
Yes, you do.
耶
Yeah.
我正巧是這方面的專家
Well, I happen to be an expert at this
因為Claudia每到周二就肚子疼
because Claudia gets a tummy rub every Tuesday.
完事了 小可愛
Yeah, all right. That's about all, kiddo.
下去吧
There you go.
你就乖乖的待在那 Rags 好嗎
You just stay right there, Rags, all right?
干的好 Owen  那些委員會成員喜歡你
Great job, Owen. Those committee members loved you.
哦 就是個老的處事技巧
Ah, it was an old management trick.
最容易團結一伙人的方法是
The easiest way to bond a group
找個外人 無情的嘲笑他
is pick an outsider, relentlessly tease him,
給他起傻外號
and give him a goofy nickname.
謝謝你成為我們的樂子 零食包
Thanks for being a good sport, snack pack.
我看了這份千年發展計劃提案
You know, I've been going over this millennium project proposal.
這里面有些很好的內容
There's some great stuff in here.
我覺得你應該淡化那個 呃
I do think you should tone down the, uh...
世界末日 人類滅亡的內容
The, uh, armageddon end of days rhetoric.
別擔心 Michael
No need to worry, Michael.
我有好消息
I have some good news.
意指受上帝指派 來拯救世人的救主
我是彌賽亞
I'm the messiah.
這很好笑 很棒
That's... that's a good joke. That's great.
應該以這個做開場白 他們會開心的
You start with that, you're gonna keep 'em light.
不 Michael 我是認真的
Uh, no, Michael. I'm serious.
天選之人 萬王之王
The chosen one. The king of kings.
傳說中的耶穌
The Alpha and the Omega.
你眼前的
You're looking at...
正是他
Him.
真是好消息
Well, that is good news.
Owen 如果這是玩笑
Look, Owen, if this is some kind of joke,
我這么說吧 很好笑的
let me just say, uh, good one.
我聽懂了 呃 哈哈
I get it. That's, uh... Ha!
我也很震驚 相信我
I'm as shocked as you are, believe me.
這是很大的責任
This is a big responsibility.
我的意思是
I mean...
你看這個
Look at this.
未完成事項
Things to do.
驅逐邪惡的撒旦和邪惡勢力
Banish Satan and the forces of evil...
重建耶路撒冷
Build the new Jerusalem...
買牛奶
Buy milk.
牛奶
Milk!
我總是忘記買牛奶
I keep forgetting to pick up milk.
Owen 你不是認真的吧
Owen, you can't be serious.
你看 Michael
L-look, Michael.
我知道 我應該獨自完成這些事
I know I'm supposed to be able to do this all by myself,
畢竟我是上帝之子
being the son of God and all,
但是我感到許多壓力
but I'm feeling a lot of pressure,
所以我就想 也許你可以幫助我
so I was thinking... maybe you could help me.
你要我幫你 幫什么
You want me to help you, what?
驅逐撒旦 建立上帝的王國
Banish Satan and establish God's kingdom on earth?
如果你不太忙的話
If you're not too busy.
你知道你讓我陷于什么處境嗎
Do you have any idea the position you've put me in?
這是個很重要的計劃 我擔保了你
I mean, this is an important project. I vouched for you.
我在市長面前為了你冒風險
I put myself on the line with the mayor for you.
Owen 如果媒體決定
Oh, Owen, if the press decide
公開的批評這個千年發展計劃項目
to publicly criticize this millennium program,
你覺得我該怎么回應
how do you think I should respond?
汝應該摧毀那些違抗你意志的人
Thou shall smite those who defy your will...
踩著他們
From the soles of your feet
的頭顱前進
to the crowns of their heads!
他的意思是 "別理他們"
He says, "Go negative."
- 所以說你認為會沒事的  - 當然
- So you think we'll be ok?  - Absolutely.
- 感謝上帝  - 不客氣
- Thank God.  - Don't mention it.
我居然在給狗做嘴對嘴人工呼吸
I can't believe I'm giving mouth-to-mouth to a dog.
哦 天哪 天哪
Oh, God! Oh, God!
他們在電影里是怎么做的
What do they do in the movies?
別死啊 別死啊
Don't die on me! Don't you die on me!
誰
Yeah?
Paul 開門
Paul, open up.
我給Rags帶來特別款待
I brought Rags a special treat.
Rags要不要來個骨頭餅干呢
Does Rags want a little cookie wookie?
呃 等下
Uh... Just a second.
好 進來 要用力推門
Ok, ok, come in, but give the door a good shove,
門有點緊
because it sticks.
啊啊啊啊
Ahhhhhhhhhhhh!
不
Oh, no!
門打到了Rags的頭
You hit Rags in the head with the door
你殺了它
and you killed him!
哦 不
Oh, no.
他沒事吧
Is he ok?
不 它絕對死了
No, he's definitely dead!
別死啊 別死啊
Don't you die on me. Don't you die on me!
這不管用的
Aw, that doesn't work.
他說他是上帝
So he said he's God.
還記得昨晚在我的櫥柜上
Remember last night on my kitchen counter?
你還說你是上帝
You said you were God.
不 我說的是我像是上帝
No, I said I was like a God.
而且 你也同意
And... and you agreed.
同意了4遍
4 times.
你會想出辦法的
You'll figure something out.
對不起 我打擾你們了嗎
I'm sorry. Am I interrupting?
我們 沒有 沒有
Oh, us? No... no... no.
她是 女同性戀
She's... she's a lesbian.
枉我教了你那么多 你還是睡了你的下屬
After all I taught you, sleeping with a member of your staff?
你不是應該用碑文給我建議嗎
Shouldn't you be giving me this advice on stone tablets?
我就知道 我就知道會這樣
I knew it. I knew this would happen.
當你告訴別人你是上帝之子
You tell people you're the son of God
別人就會把你當歸入異類
and suddenly you're pigeon-holed.
Owen 我也不想這么做
Owen, I don't want to have to do this,
但是我必須把你剔除出千年發展計劃
but I've gotta take you off the millennium project.
太高調了
It's just too high profile.
你開除我
You're firing me?
是
Yeah.
你翅膀硬了啊
Wow. You've really grown some teeth.
Michael 我能做好的
Michael, I... I can do this.
政治依然存在于我的生命
It's still a part of who I am.
相信我 求你了
Believe in me, please.
我也想 但是
I would like to, but...
曾有一次你希望我相信你 我做到了
there was a time when you wanted me to believe in you, and I did.
好吧 你要專注于政治 不許再傳教
All right, you stick to politics, ok? No more preaching.
好的
Ok.
- 保證嗎  - 我向
- Promise?  - I swear...
我自己發誓
To me.
Stuart 既然你了解情況
All right, Stuart. Since you know what's going on,
我也許需要你的建議
I might as well get your advice.
你睡過多少女人
How many women have you slept with?
粗略的嗎(音同粗暴地)
Roughly?
我不想知道你怎么睡人家的 你個變態
I don't care how you did it, you sicko.
Marie想讓我教她關于性的一切 是我
Marie wants me to teach her about sex. Me!
沒問題 我知道該怎么辦
No problem, I know exactly what to do.
嘿  Stacy
Hey, Stacy.
我們的小James有新女朋友了嗎
Our little James has a new girlfriend.
是嗎 這表示你和你媽媽分手了
Oh, really? So you broke up with your mom?
他壓力山大
Hey, he's under a lot of pressure.
這個女人需要人滿足她的欲望
This woman is looking for someone to satisfy her sexually.
讓她聯系這個家伙
Just have her call this guy.
友善些
Be nice.
租個電影 叫<愛你九周半>
Rent the movie 9 1/2 weeks.
她是對的  James 你看了那部電影后
She's right, James. You watch that movie,
絕對能長知識
you are guaranteed to get some.
酷
Cool.
什么知識
Some what?
市長先生
Mr. Mayor.
怎么樣了啊 零食包
Oh, how's it going, snack pack?
我正要出發去千年發展計劃大會
Well, I'm on my way to the millennium conference, sir.
你想參加嗎
You care to join me?
是的 我本人很欣賞Owen
Yeah, great. You know, I like Owen a lot,
但是我有些小小的擔心他老提及
but I'm a little concerned about his constant invoking of...
關于上帝那部分嗎
God, sir?
是的
That's it.
我的意思是 我對偶爾提及
I mean, I'm totally comfortable with
上帝是沒有問題的
the occasional reference to, uh...
但是在這個環境下
G-dash-d, but in this context...
先生 我代表Owen向您保證
sir, I've spoken to Owen, and he's assured me
他不會把這個計劃轉變成宗教場景的
he's not going to turn this into some religious spectacle.
模仿著名油畫<最后的晚餐>
這怎么有些眼熟
Why does this look familiar?
我感到很自責
I just feel so guilty.
Carter 也許是他命數已盡
Carter, look. Maybe it was just his time.
你知道的  就算你沒用們打它的頭
You know, if you didn't hit him with the door,
別人也可能會
you know, somebody might of... I don't know,
把鎮紙砸在他頭上
dropped a paper weight on his head.
Paul 有點同情心吧
Paul, be a little sensitive.
真是的 他的狗剛剛死掉
Really. The man's dog just died.
死了
Dead.
永遠離開了
Gone forever.
死了 死翹翹了 死得透透的
Dead, dead, dead.
他還有那么多生命沒有度過
He just had so much living left to do.
不 他沒有
No, he didn't.
他的
His, uh...
他的真名是
His real name was, uh...
Reginald R. Ragamuffin三世
Reginald R. Ragamuffin III.
他是社區中唯一叫得出自己姓名首字母的狗
He's the only dog on the block who could say his own initials.
"Rrrrrrrr"
這么多年
so many years.
好多回憶
So many memories.
Keep On Loving You---Reo Speedwagon
我都不相信你會殺了自己的狗
I can't believe you killed your own dog.
嘿 別說了
Hey, cut it out!
是個事故 好了吧
It was an accident, all right?!
他也不會下地獄的
And he's not going to hell!
他不會 他不會
He's not! He's not!
Winston政府
Well, here's to the Winston administration
照亮了通往千年發展計劃的道路
blazing a path into the new millennium.
對于那些異教徒
Whoa-oa-oa-oa to the infidels...
他們會被燃燒的地獄吞噬
Who will burn in a fiery hell!
很高興與您共事
Well, it was nice working with ya.
這是我從<愛你九周半>中學來的
Ok. This is a little something from 9 1/2 weeks.
我管它叫"脫衣舞挑逗你"
I call it "The striptease."
- 哦 不  - 怎么了
- Oh, no!  - What?
不 我是去買的是<愛你九周半>的原聲碟
No! I went out to get the soundtrack from 9 1/2 weeks,
但是我不小心買到的是<九周半學彈班卓琴>
but I accidentally got 9 1/2 weeks to learn the banjo.
James 你知道的 我們并不需要
James, you know, we really don't need to...
可以了 你和我
All right. You and me...
我們要離開這里
We're gettin' out of here.
至于你
And you...
明天你就死定了
You're dead tomorrow.
Stacy 你怎么知道的
Uh, st-Stacy, how did you know?
你好 室友
Howdy, partner!
嘿 音量放大點
Hey, turn that up.
你知道 Owen
You know, Owen...
事實上
actually...
Michael 我要退出這個千年發展計劃
Michael, I'm going to take myself off this millennium project.
我理解的
Well, hey, I understand.
你還有很多事的
You got a lot going on.
也許還沒有驅逐撒旦
Probably haven't even banished Satan.
- 沒  - 牛奶也沒買吧
- Nope.  - Or bought milk.
啊 該死的
Ah, damn!
很抱歉 事情進展的不順利
Sorry it didn't work out.
別 我不關心這份工作
Don't be. I don't care about the job.
這不是我來這里的原因
That's not why I came here.
那你為什么來這里
Why did you come here?
我來這里來看你
I came here to see you.
我想你 Michael
I miss you, Michael.
Michael 我過去常說的那句話是什么來著
Michael, what was it I used to say
帶領一支高效的競選團隊
was the number one rule
的第一準則是
of leading an effective campaign staff?
不要以為自己知道所有的答案
Don't think you know all the answers.
可憐的Rags
Poor Rags.
好狗狗
Goo-oo-ood dog.
他活了
He's alive!
這是個神跡
It's a miracle.
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
哦 我就是不能歇一會兒
Oh, man. I just can't catch a break.
我真是個可惡的人
I'm such a horrible person.
進來
Yeah, come in.
Carter
Carter!
Carter 他活了
Carter, he's alive!
你沒殺了它
You didn't kill him.
我太高興了
Oh, I'm so happy for you.
你真是個好朋友
You are such a good friend.
哦 Carter
Aw, Carter, aw...
啊 他咬我
Ow! He bit me.
我以前做過 現在還能再來一遍
I did it once, I'll do it again.
什么
What?
呃
Um...
是我們玩的一個游戲 去撿
It's a game we play... fetch.
我應該用棍子的
I should use a stick.
電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入
官方網站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@電波字幕組